mountainx.com 2010-12-06

# Mountain Xpress privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

Mountain Xpress has developed this privacy policy as part of its commitment to protecting individuals’ privacy.

When you visit our Web pages, we automatically log your Internet domain or address (IP address), geographic location and the Web location you clicked from, so we can tell how many people visit each page and how they find us. If you click on an ad, this is recorded so we can inform advertisers how many people respond to their ads. Some of our pages may place a small text file (a "cookie") on your computer so we can identify it when you visit. Most Web browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. However, some Web features and services may not function properly with cookies disabled.

We use Google Analytics to monitor and analyze traffic on our site. Most of our pages contain a code that causes Google to place a cookie on your computer to enable this monitoring. For information on how Google uses its cookies, consult the [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

We or our advertisers may use a third-party advertising company to serve some of the ads you see on our site. This company may use information about your visits to our and other Web sites in order to provide ads that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving ads to our site, an advertising company may place a cookie on your computer. 

Our sites may ask you for personally identifying information – such as your name, address and email address – for various reasons, such as: You are purchasing something, registering for our site as a member, taking a survey. You may refuse to provide the information. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under age 13.

Our services give you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. We will not automatically send you information/offers you do not want. You must choose to receive them.

If you are purchasing a product or service through the Xpress websites you may be asked to enter financial information (such as credit card numbers, and/or billing address). Credit card numbers are never stored by Xpress and are used only during the billing process. We use the reputable [Authorize.Net payment gateway](http://www.authorize.net/) to process credit cards. Their security and privacy statements can be found on [their website](http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/).

When gathering personally identifying information, we will not release any such information to third parties unless: 1) at the time of gathering the information, we specifically state our intention to do so, 2) at some later time, we ask for and receive your permission to release the information, 3) if at any time you give us your consent, 4) we believe in good faith that we are legally required to do so, 5) there is an emergency involving personal danger, 6) you have vandalized our site or behaved in a manner that warrants our contacting governmental regulatory authorities or your Internet service provider.

If you are a member of our sites, may visit your Personal Settings page to edit your profile and other information. You can also delete your account completely by contacting [webmaster@mountainx.com](mailto:webmaster@mountainx.com).

Our Web sites contain links to other sites offered by other parties. These links are provided for reference and convenience only. These other sites are not under our control and have their own data and privacy practices.

The Web is a rapidly evolving system, and our privacy policies are likely to change from time to time; any changes will be posted here as soon as they go into effect.

### Opt-Out

Our sites provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

### Delete/Deactivate

Our sites give users the following options for removing their information from our database, to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service.

If you are a member of our sites, visit your Personal Settings page and delete your account; otherwise you can send an email with your stated request to [webmaster@mountainx.com](mailto:webmaster@mountainx.com).

Change/Modify Our sites give users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. If you are a member of our sites, visit your Personal Settings page and delete your account; otherwise you can send an email with your stated request to [webmaster@mountainx.com](mailto:webmaster@mountainx.com).

Contacting our Web Sites If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our sites, or your dealings with any of our sites, [contact us](http://www.mountainx.com/info/contact)  or write or email us at:

Webmaster or Publisher Mountain Xpress/mountainx.com PO Box 144 Asheville, NC 28802

Or [webmaster@mountainx.com](mailto:webmaster@mountainx.com)

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please write to [webmaster@mountainx.com](mailto:webmaster@mountainx.com).

Effective Date: Dec. 11, 2008
